Loena Lewis - Bleeding Love
莱昂娜・路易斯 ― 伤心的爱
Closed off from love
心与爱一刀两断
I didn't need the pain
我不再需要感受伤痛
Once or twice was enough
一两次煎熬足矣
And it was all in vain
往事不过如一场春梦
Time starts to pass
时光已开始流逝
Before you know it you're frozen
岁月转眼会将你尘封
But something happened
可回首曾经的我
For the very first time with you
在与你邂逅的那一刻
My heart melts into the ground
整个心悄然融化
Found something true
你是我寻觅已久的爱
And everyone's looking round
身边人满脸惊讶
Thinking I'm going crazy
全都以为我是着了魔
But I don't care what they say
可他们说的我不理会
I'm in love with you
因为我爱上了你
They try to pull me away
他们只想着将我拽回
But they don't know the truth
怎知我力不从心
My heart's crippled by the veinn
那不停痉挛的血管啊
That I keep on closing
早已将我心堵塞
You cut me open and I
你划开我心，任凭它
Keep bleeding
不停地滴着
Keep, keep bleeding love
滴着滴着爱的血
I keep bleeding
它不停地滴着
I keep, keep bleeding love
它滴着滴着爱的血
Keep bleeding
不停地滴着
Keep, keep bleeding love
滴着滴着爱的血
You cut me open
你划开我心
Trying hard not to hear
用双手拼命捂住耳朵
But they talk so loud
他们却扯起嗓子
Their piercing sounds fill my ears
尖声利语直插我心窝
Try to fill me with doubt
欲乱我所有情思
Yet I know that the goal
可我懂他们的本意是
Is to keep me from falling
阻止我向深渊里坠落
But nothing's greater
可有什么比得上
Than the rush that comes with your embrace
你怀抱中我心的悸动
And in this world of loneliness
在孤单寂寞的世界里
I see your face
唯可见你的面容
Yet everyone around me
可我身边的每一个人
Thinks that I'm going crazy
全都以为我是着了魔
Maybe, maybe
也行，也许
But I don't care what they say
可他们说的我不理会
I'm in love with you
因为我爱上了你
They try to pull me away
他们只想着将我拽回
But they don't know the truth
怎知我力不从心
My heart's crippled by the veinn
那不停痉挛的血管啊
That I keep on closing
早已将我心堵塞
You cut me open and I
你划开我心，任凭它
Keep bleeding
不停地滴着
Keep, keep bleeding love
滴着滴着爱的血
I keep bleeding
它不停地滴着
I keep, keep bleeding love
它滴着滴着爱的血
Keep bleeding
不停地滴着
Keep, keep bleeding love
滴着滴着爱的血
You cut me open
你划开我心
And it's draining all of me
我爱的鲜血行将流尽
Oh they find it hard to believe
噢,他们如何能信
I'll be wearing these scars
我会将心上这些伤疤
For everyone to see
裸露给每一个人
I don't care what they say
可他们说的我不理会
I'm in love with you
因为我爱上了你
They try to pull me away
他们只想着将我拽回
But they don't know the truth
怎知我力不从心
My heart's crippled by the vein
那不停痉挛的血管啊
That I keep on closing
早已将我心堵塞
You cut me open and I
你划开我心，任凭它
Keep bleeding
不停地滴着
Keep, keep bleeding love
滴着滴着爱的血
I keep bleeding love
它不停地滴着
I keep, keep bleeding love
它滴着滴着爱的血
Keep bleeding
不停地滴着
Keep, keep bleeding love
滴着滴着爱的血
You cut me open and I
你划开我心，任凭它
Keep bleeding
不停地滴着
Keep, keep bleeding love
滴着滴着爱的血
I keep bleeding love
它不停地滴着
I keep, keep bleeding love
它滴着滴着爱的血
Keep bleeding
不停地滴着
Keep, keep bleeding love
滴着滴着爱的血
You cut me open and I
你划开我心，任凭它
Keep bleeding
不停地滴着
Keep, keep bleeding love
滴着滴着爱的血